<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ans_array">
        <item name="ans1">Daily Journal entries will be available between 2:00 PM EST and 12:00 AM EST (midnight) every day until the study ends. You should submit your journal entry once every day between these times./n/nBecause we are asking about your online experiences, the best time to submit your entry would be after most of your online interactions for the day. For example, if you use social media or send texts until you go to bed, try to submit your journal entry close to your bedtime./n/nYou can also customize when you want to be reminded to submit your journal entries. For example, if you plan to submit entries every day before bed, you can set the reminder to notify you right before your bedtime. From the 30 Days dashboard, just tap Settings, then Daily Reminder.</item>
        <item name="ans2">You can submit a screenshot at any time. Share a Screenshot gives you the opportunity to share your experiences with the researchers close in time to when they happen. Any online interaction or situation you feel is risky should be shared as soon as possible to help us better understand your online experiences. Screenshots are secured and encrypted and will be anonymized in our research.</item>
        <item name="ans3">You can earn up to $115 total for completing this study. Here is the breakdown:/n/nYou will receive $1.50 for each journal entry submitted and approved by the researcher. In total, $45 for 30 journal entries (one for each day of the study)./n/nThis 30-day study is broken down into 6 periods of 5 days each. You will receive a $5 bonus for each period if you submit a journal entry for all 5 days within the period and the researcher approves them. If you also submit a screenshot during the 5-day period and it is approved by the researcher, you will receive an additional $5 bonus. In total, you can earn up to $60 in bonuses ($10 for each period)./n/nFinally, you can earn $10 for completing the post-survey./n/nBreak down: $45 (diary entries) + $60 (bonuses) + $10 (post survey) = $115</item>
        <item name="ans4">Once you complete the entire study and the researcher approves, you will be emailed an Amazon gift card for the total amount you earned.</item>
        <item name="ans5">The study is finished once the number of “days left in study” at the top of the dashboard reaches zero and you complete the post-survey. You will also receive a final email from the researcher confirming the end of your participation.</item>
        <item name="ans7">30 Days collects information that helps us get a better understanding of your online experiences. This includes information that you submit yourself (daily journal entries and screenshots), a list of all the apps installed on the device, the time spent using each app, and the total time spent using the device each day. We do not collect data from any of your apps, nor do we track what you do in each app</item>
        <item name="ans8">Your user data and Share a Screenshot text descriptions are stored in a password-protected database on Amazon Web Services (AWS). Your device data and Share a Screenshot images are stored in an AWS Simple Storage Service (S3) bucket that also uses server-side AES-256 encryption. Daily Journal uses a well-known and secure survey platform called Qualtrics to record responses. All data is encrypted in transit using HTTPS/n/nAll of this is a fancy way of saying, we’re serious about your privacy and protecting your data./n/nAny research published from this study will only present aggregated or anonymized information, meaning no results will be published that would allow you to be personally identified./n/nHowever, if data collected from this study strongly indicates that you are at serious risk of physical injury, sexual abuse, mental injury, or physical neglect, we are required by law to report these types of imminent risks to the proper authorities. Also, the IRB and its representatives may inspect and copy your data to ensure the ethical compliance of this research is being upheld. /n/nAll of your data will be anonymized 2 years after the last participant has been recruited. This data will be used for follow-up questions about the study and to invite participants to future studies. All of your data will be completely destroyed after a minimum of 5 years according to UCF policy.</item>
        <item name="ans9">For questions or concerns about the study or research, or for technical support with the 30 Days app, tap Contact the Team below. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>