<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ans_array">
        <item name="ans1">Daily Journal will be available at 2:00 PM EST every day until the study ends. It will become unavailable at 12:00 AM EST (midnight). You should submit your journal entry once every day between these times. Because we are asking about your online experiences, the best time to submit your entry would be after most of your online interactions for the day. For example, if you use social media or send texts until you go to bed, then try to submit your journal entry close to your bed time.\n\nYou can customize when you want to be reminded to submit your journal entries. For example, if you plan to submit entries every day before bed, you can set the reminder to right before your bed time. From the 30 Days dashboard, just tap Settings, then Daily Journal Reminder.</item>
        <item name="ans2">Share My screenshots gives you the opportunity to share your experiences with the researchers close in time to when they happen. Any online interaction or situation that you feel is risky should be shared with us as soon as you can. Share My screenshots lets you describe and attach a screenshot of the experience to give us a better idea of the kinds of risky situations teens experience online. This data is secured and encrypted, and will be anonymized in our research. </item>
        <item name="ans3">You will receive $10 for completing the pre-survey, $1.50 for each journal entry submitted, and $10 for completing the post-survey. Additionally, the 30 day study is broken up into 6 periods of 5 days each, and if you submit a journal entry for each of the 5 days within a period, you will receive a $10 bonus. Since there are 6 of these periods, you can earn up to $60 in bonuses. This means, if you submit all of your journal entries, you can earn up to $125 total for completing the study. Tap your earnings in the top right corner of the app for more details. </item>
        <item name="ans4">At the end of the study, emailed Amazon gift cards? </item>
        <item name="ans5">The study is almost finished when the green bar at the top of the app is full, and when the number of “days to go” reaches zero. When this happens, you will no longer have access to the 30 Days dashboard, and you will be asked to take the post-survey. To finish the study, complete this survey, and you will earn your final $10. </item>
        <item name="ans6">The streaks counter displays how many days in a row you have submitted your journal entry. To keep up your streak, just keep submitting your journal entries every day. If you miss a day, your streak will drop to zero. </item>
        <item name="ans7">The app collects information that you submit yourself (entries in Daily Journal and Share My screenshots), as well as some device metadata that helps us get a better understanding of teens’ social media usage (a list of all apps installed on the device, the time spent using each app, and the total time spent using the device each day).</item>
        <item name="ans8">Your user data and Share My screenshots text responses are stored in a password-protected database on Amazon Web Services (AWS) with server-side AES-256 encryption. Your device metadata and Share My screenshots screenshots are stored in an AWS Simple Storage Service (S3) bucket that also uses server-side AES-256 encryption. Daily Journal uses a well-known and secure survey platform called Qualtrics to record responses. All data is encrypted in transit using HTTPS. All of this is a fancy way of saying, we’re serious about your privacy and protecting your data.\n\nAny research published from this study will only present aggregated or anonymized information, meaning no results will be published that would allow you to be personally identified. However, if data collected from this study strongly indicates that you are at serious risk of physical injury, sexual abuse, mental injury, or physical neglect, we are required by law to report these types of imminent risks to the proper authorities. The IRB and its representatives may inspect and copy your data to ensure the ethical compliance of this research is being upheld.\n\nAll of your data will be anonymized 2 years after the last participant has been recruited. This data will be used for follow-up questions about the study and to invite participants to future studies. All of your data will be completely destroyed after a minimum of 5 years according to UCF policy.</item>
        <item name="ans9">For questions or concerns about the study and research, email Karla Badillo-Urquiola, Graduate Student PI, at kbadillo@ist.ucf.edu. For questions about or technical support for 30 Days, email Zachary Shea at zshea@knights.ucf.edu. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>